Guide to the A. B. Cook Papers 1882-1940
Montana Historical Society Archives
- A.B. Cook
  - General Correspondence
    - McIntyre Ranching Company, Ltd. (William H. McIntyre, McGrath, Alta.), 1918-1928 (Box-folder 12 / 15-16)
    - Alexander McKenzie (re Republican politics, mining venture; see also Cook Construction Company subgroup), 1909-1920 (Box-folder 12 / 17)
    - McD-McK (correspondents include A.J. McDonald, McElroy Ranch Company, James McFarlane, E.A. McHardy, Hugh McKee, W.K. McKenzie, George McKethen), 1909-1928 (Box-folder 12 / 18)
    - C.M. McLeod (Missoula Mercantile Company), 1924-1926 (Box-folder 12 / 19)
    - James and Mary McNaught (Silverton, B.C.), 1911 (Box-folder 12 / 20)
    - Taylor McNiven (Livingston, Mont.), 1926-1928 (Box-folder 12 / 21)
    - P.C. and Emelia McStravick (Kalispell, Mont.), 1922-1927 (Box-folder 12 / 22)
    - McL-McV (correspondents include John A. McLean, Walter S. McLean, William J. McLean, C.H. McLemore, Robert D. McNab, McNamara and Marlow, McNeel Marble Company, Mrs. Rory McQueen, J.H. McShane Timber Company), 1906-1928 (Box-folder 12 / 23)
    - Meagher County offices, 1917-1928 (Box-folder 12 / 24)
    - Fitch H. Medbury (re proposed sale of interest in ranch), 1924 (Box-folder 12 / 25)
    - A.J. Meloche (T.O. Ranch Company, Raton, N.M.), 1920-1921 (Box-folder 12 / 26)
    - S.R. Mercer (Missoula, Mont.), 1923-1924 (Box-folder 12 / 27)
    - Merchants National Bank (St. Paul, Minn.), 1909-1928 (Box-folder 12 / 28)
    - George Merrill (Thermopolis, Wyo.), 1924-1928 (Box-folder 12 / 29)
    - Metals Bank and Trust Company (Butte, Mont.), 1922-1928 (Box-folder 12 / 30)
    - Andrew J. Metler (Menno, S.D.), 1919-1925 (Box-folder 12 / 31)
    - Me (correspondents include L.E. Megee, Andrew Meikle, H.C. Meining Company, B.P. Melchert, Sam Melph, W.T. Merrill), 1909-1928 (Box-folder 12 / 32)
    - Midland Empire Fair; Midland Stock Show (Billings, Mont.), 1916-1928 (Box-folder 12 / 33)
    - Midland Linseed Products Company (Minneapolis, Minn.), 1917-1919 (Box-folder 12 / 34)
    - Miller (correspondents include Miller and Lux, Inc., A.W. Miller, Miller Brothers, Curtis J. Miller, D.S. Miller, Miller Development Company, Robert J. Miller), 1917-1928 (Box-folder 13 / 1)
    - Minneapolis Army and Navy Store, 1922-1923 (Box-folder 13 / 2)
    - Minnesota Valley Canning Company, 1924-1926 (Box-folder 13 / 3)
    - Missoula (correspondents include city and county offices, Missoula Chamber of Commerce, Missoula Mercantile Company, Missoula Trust and Savings Bank), 1915-1927 (Box-folder 13 / 4)
    - Mi (correspondents include Miami Conservancy District, Austin Middleton, Mid-States Oil Company, George R. Milburn, G.M. Miles, Millers Mutual Casualty Company, Charles A. Millie, C.J. Milligan Company, W.H. Miner, Minnesota Club, Frank D. Miracle, T.E. Mitchell and Son), 1909-1928 (Box-folder 13 / 5)
    - George P. and E.A. Moeller (Hettinger, N.D.), 1924 (Box-folder 13 / 6)
    - A. Moier and Son (Reichle, Mont.), 1919 (Box-folder 13 / 7)
    - Manley Moline (Circle, Mont.), 1924-1925 (Box-folder 13 / 8)
    - Monnett and Hamilton (Dayton, Wash.), 1921 (Box-folder 13 / 9)
    - Montana. Agricultural Experiment Station (includes C.N. Arnett, R.C. McChord, Clyde McKee, Louis Vinke, F.M. Harrington, H.W. Vaughan, Purcell Bill establishing Fort Keogh station), 1918-1928 (Box-folder 13 / 10-11)
    - Montana. Agricultural Extension Service, 1923-1928 (Box-folder 13 / 12)
    - Montana. Board of Railroad Commissioners, 1918-1924 (Box-folder 13 / 13)
    - Montana. Board of Stock Commissioners, 1908-1910 (Box-folder 13 / 14)
    - Montana. Dept. of Agriculture, Labor and Industry (includes State Fair), 1921-1927 (Box-folder 13 / 15)
    - Montana. Dept. of Fish and Game; Fish and Game Commission, 1917-1928 (Box-folder 13 / 16)
    - Montana. Dept. of State Lands and Farm Loans, 1909-1928 (Box-folder 13 / 17)
    - Montana. Governor, 1909-1927 (Box-folder 13 / 18)
    - Montana. Industrial Accident Board, 1916-1918 (Box-folder 13 / 19)
    - Montana. Livestock Commission, 1919-1928 (Box-folder 13 / 20)
    - Montana. Livestock Sanitary Board (W.J. Butler, State Veterinarian), 1917-1928 (Box-folder 13 / 21)
    - Montana. Secretary of State, 1917-1928 (Box-folder 13 / 22)
    - Montana. Stallion Registration Board, 1910-1922 (Box-folder 13 / 23)
    - Montana. State Fire Marshal, 1919-1926 (Box-folder 13 / 24)
    - Montana. [miscellaneous state agencies], 1907-1928 (Box-folder 13 / 25)
    - Montana Club, 1918-1928 (Box-folder 13 / 26)
    - Montana Deaconess Home, 1915-1917 (Box-folder 13 / 27)
    - Montana Farmer, 1916-1927 (Box-folder 13 / 28)
    - Montana Flour Mills Company, 1921-1927 (Box-folder 13 / 29)
    - Montana Hereford Breeders Association (includes C.C. Davis, L. Chatterton), 1918-1925 (Box-folder 13 / 30)
    - Montana Life Insurance Company, 1927-1928 (Box-folder 13 / 31)
    - Montana Livestock Finance Corporation (A.T. Hibbard), 1922-1926 (Box-folder 13 / 32)
    - Montana State Fair [private], 1909-1921 (Box-folder 13 / 33)
    - Montana Stock Growers Association, 1917-1928 (Box-folder 13 / 34)
    - Montana Trust and Savings Bank (Helena, Mont.), 1915-1927 (Box-folder 13 / 35)
    - Montana Wool Growers Association, 1921-1926 (Box-folder 13 / 36)
    - Montana (correspondents include Montana Automobile Association, Montana Commercial and Labor League, Montana Culvert and Flume Company, Montana Duroc-Jersey Breeders Association, Montana Joint Stock Land Bank, Montana Livestock Pavilion Company, Montana Mercantile Company, Montana Muskrat Breeders Inc., Montana Newspaper Association, Montana Purebred Sheep Association, Montana Ranches Company, Montana Raw Fur Company, Montana Southern Railway Company, Montana Sportsmen's Association, Montana Tax-Payers' Association, Montana Wool Cooperative Marketing Association), 1910-1928 (Box-folder 13 / 37)
    - C.F. Morris (Havre, Mont., re Brown's Coulee oil drilling), 1927 (Box-folder 13 / 38)
    - George H. Moses (U.S. Senator, New Hampshire), 1924-1925 (Box-folder 13 / 39)
    - Burton C. Mossman (Roswell, N.M.), 1926-1928 (Box-folder 14 / 1)
    - Matteson M. Mounts (Bismarck, N.D.), 1909-1928 (Box-folder 14 / 2)
    - Mousel Brothers (Cambridge, Nebr.), 1909-1922 (Box-folder 14 / 3)
    - Mo (correspondents include Moffett Studio, Ed Monahan, C.F. Monson, J.H. Montgomery, Montreal and Southern Counties Railway Company, Montross Metal Casket Company, E.L. Moorman, C.F. Morris, Morrison Brothers, W.J. Moss, R.S. Mossman, C.H. Moulton, Mount Royal Hotel Company), 1909-1928 (Box-folder 14 / 4)
    - George M. Mungas (Philipsburg, Mont.), 1922-1928 (Box-folder 14 / 5)
    - Mu-My (correspondents include C.S. Muffly, W.P. Murphy, Murphy Wholesale Grocery Company, Kenneth Myers), 1907-1924 (Box-folder 14 / 6)
    - T.Y. Nakagawa (Missoula, Mont.), 1923 (Box-folder 14 / 7)
    - National Bank of Montana (Helena, Mont.), 1909-1928 (Box-folder 14 / 8)
    - National Duroc-Jersey Record Association (J.R. Pfander), 1918-1924 (Box-folder 14 / 9)
    - National Irrigation Congress, 1909 (Box-folder 14 / 10)
    - National Live Stock and Meat Board (includes report by R.C. Pollock), 1927-1928 (Box-folder 14 / 11)
    - National Marketing Committee, 1915 (Box-folder 14 / 12)
    - National Wool Warehouse and Storage Company, 1922-1923 (Box-folder 14 / 13)
    - National (correspondents include National Agricultural Society, National Association of Farm Equipment Manufacturers, National Economic League, National Farm News, National Institute of Progressive Farming, National Land Company, National Life Insurance Company, National Western Stock Show, National Wool Growers Association), 1915-1927 (Box-folder 14 / 14)
    - Louis Nelson (N.D. and Ont.), 1906 (Box-folder 14 / 15)
    - Thomas Newland (Helena, Mont.), 1915-1917 (Box-folder 14 / 16)
    - C.C. Newman (Dillon, Mont.), 1915-1926 (Box-folder 14 / 17)
    - Na-Ni (correspondents include Arthur C. Nash, Nay Brothers, Nebraska Governor, Nebraska Consolidated Mills Company, R. Neusch, Guy D. Nevills, New York Evening Post, Nichols and Shepard Company, Nixon Live Stock Commission Company), 1910-1928 (Box-folder 14 / 18)
    - Northern Pacific Railway Company (includes lawsuit, 1921; time of men fighting railroad caused fires, 1926), 1908-1928 (Box-folder 14 / 19)
    - Northern Pacific Railway Company. Land Dept. (includes leases, receipts, etc.), 1914-1928 (Box-folder 14 / 20)
    - Northwest Hereford Cattle Breeders Association (Reno Banks), 1920-1926 (Box-folder 14 / 21)
    - Northwest (correspondents include Northwest Livestock Association, Northwest Regional Advisory Board), 1915-1924 (Box-folder 14 / 22)
    - Northwestern (correspondents include Northwestern Distributing Company, Northwestern Electric Equipment Company, Northwestern Engineering Company, Northwestern Hereford Breeder, Northwestern Mutual Life Insurance Company, Northwestern Society of New York, Northwestern Stockman and Farmer), 1909-1926 (Box-folder 14 / 23)
    - Nor-West Farmer, 1917-1927 (Box-folder 14 / 24)
    - No-Ny (correspondents include Pat Normandin, Edwin L. Norris, Northern Grain and Warehouse Company, Northern Nevada Purebred Association, E.A. Noyes and Son, Nye and Jenks Grain Company), 1913-1928 (Box-folder 14 / 25)
    - John E. O'Connor (Portland, Ore.), 1916 (Box-folder 15 / 1)
    - P.A. O'Farrell (Montreal, Que.), 1909 (Box-folder 15 / 2)
    - J.C. Oliver and Sons (Herman Oliver, John Day, Ore.), 1921-1928 (Box-folder 15 / 3)
    - Charles E. Orchard (Denver, Colo.), 1925-1928 (Box-folder 15 / 4)
    - O (correspondents include W.L. Ober, C.N. O'Donel, J.C. O'Hara enclosing copy of his A Mining Romance, Oklahoma Live Stock News, Thomas O'Laughlin, Olds Motor Works, Henry Oliver, Omaha Chamber of Commerce, Axel Carlson Onrud, Ossining School, Handel E. Owen), 1907-1928 (Box-folder 15 / 5)
    - Pacific Northwest Farm Trio, 1919-1926 (Box-folder 15 / 6)
    - John E. Painter (representative of several live stock associations), 1918-1924 (Box-folder 15 / 7)
    - Parchen Drug Company (Helena, Mont.), 1922-1925 (Box-folder 15 / 8)
    - Pa (correspondents include Pacific Bond and Mortgage Company, Pacific Coast Pipe Company, Pacific International Live Stock Exposition, M.S. Parker, Willis F. Parker, Thomas G. Paterson, H.F. Patterson, G.T. Paul, Peter Pauly, Oscar L. Payne), 1906-1928 (Box-folder 15 / 9)
    - Marguerite Peacock (Drummond, Mont.), 1926-1928 (Box-folder 15 / 10)
    - Peking University (China), 1924 (Box-folder 15 / 11)
    - Lewis Penwell Company (Helena, Mont.), 1917-1923 (Box-folder 15 / 12)
    - J.L. Perron (Montreal, Que.), 1918-1926 (Box-folder 15 / 13)
    - R.F. Pettigrew (Sioux Falls, S.D.), 1921-1925 (Box-folder 15 / 14)
    - Pe (correspondents include George D. Pease, Pelletier and Crowther, Pence Automobile Company, Frank Peterson, John Peterson, Andrew Petrie), 1909-1927 (Box-folder 15 / 15)
    - Phelps Ranch (Eugene and L.G. Phelps, Meeteetse, Wyo.), 1919-1928 (Box-folder 15 / 16)
    - Ph (correspondents include H.W. Phelps, Edwin A. Phillips, P.M. Phillips), 1910-1926 (Box-folder 15 / 17)
    - Pickering Farm (W.A. and W.R. Pickering, Belton, Mo.), 1918-1927 (Box-folder 15 / 18)
    - Harry W. Pickett (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1906-1907 (Box-folder 15 / 19)
    - Pioneers of Eastern Montana, 1912-1928 (Box-folder 15 / 20)
    - Pi-Pl (correspondents include A.W. Pieper, Charles H. Pierce, Piggly Wiggly Montana Company, H.H. Pigott, David Pimperton), 1909-1928 (Box-folder 15 / 21)
    - Political: re manganese tariff, 1922 (Box-folder 15 / 22)
    - Political: re proposal to move Forest Service to Dept. of Interior, 1921-1922 (Box-folder 15 / 23)
    - Charles Pollack (Craig, Mont.), 1919-1924 (Box-folder 15 / 24)
    - Norman S. Poole (Townsend, Mont.), 1912-1925 (Box-folder 15 / 25)
    - T.C. Power; T.C. Power Company; T.C. Power Motor Car Company, 1906-1928 (Box-folder 15 / 26)
    - Po (correspondents include J.E. Poole, C.R. Pope Company, Porter-Davidson Company, Louville Porter, Portland Cattle Loan Company, Portland Union Stock Yards, Potrero Ranch, W.O. Pound and Sons, J.D. Powell, William Powers), 1906-1928 (Box-folder 15 / 27)
    - Charles Preece (Waterloo, Mont.), 1908-1910 (Box-folder 15 / 28)
    - The Producer, 1919-1923 (Box-folder 15 / 29)
    - Pr-Py (correspondents include Pratt-Thompson Construction Company, Charles N. Pray, Robert A. Pringle, George Prior, W.O. Protsman, Pullman Company), 1909-1928 (Box-folder 15 / 30)
    - Quealy Land and Livestock Company (John Quealy, Hanna, Wyo.), 1926-1928 (Box-folder 15 / 31)
    - Quinn-Shepardson Company (Minneapolis, Minn.), 1917-1919 (Box-folder 15 / 32)
    - Q (correspondents include Quanah Cotton Oil Company, Thomas B. Quaw, Queen Incubator Company, Benjamin Quigley, Tom Quing, Nora Quinlan), 1914-1927 (Box-folder 15 / 33)
    - Jack T. Ramey (Fort Yates, N.D.), 1925-1928 (Box-folder 15 / 34)
    - Wellington Rankin (Helena, Mont.), 1928 (Box-folder 15 / 35)
    - Rea Brothers (Billings, Mont.), 1916-1926 (Box-folder 15 / 36)
    - Reinig Company (Helena, Mont.), 1922-1926 (Box-folder 15 / 37)
    - Ra-Re (correspondents include A.E. Ragan, A.A.D. Rahn, Realty Company, N.R. Reasoner, George Rebedeaux, Carl L. Reed, Harry C. Reed, W.C. Reed, K.M. Reeves, Regina Agricultural and Industrial Exhibition, J.H. Reniger, Fred Reppert), 1908-1917 (Box-folder 16 / 1)
    - Ringling (correspondents include Ringling and Work, R.T. Ringling Ranch, Ringling State Bank), 1922-1926 (Box-folder 16 / 2)
    - Dave Risk (Kansas City, Mo.), 1917-1922 (Box-folder 16 / 3)
    - Ri (correspondents include D.E. Richards, Howard F. Riddle, Ridgefield Sheep Feeding Yards), 1918-1928 (Box-folder 16 / 4)
    - Robinson Cartage and Storage Company (Orilia, Ont.), 1912-1923 (Box-folder 16 / 5)
    - Charles O. Robinson and Company, Livestock Commission, 1922-1928 (Box-folder 16 / 6)
    - Rocky Mountain Club of New York, 1907-1928 (Box-folder 16 / 7)
    - Nick Rorvig (Helena, Mont.), 1917-1928 (Box-folder 16 / 8)
    - Rosenbaum Brothers and Company, 1915-1928 (Box-folder 16 / 9)
    - Ro (correspondents include George Robb, E.L. Robbins, O.P. Roberts, T.H. Robertson, Harry Robinson, Rock Island Stove Company, Rocky Mountain Fertilizer Company, Ralph Rodriguez, Joseph Roke, Leverett S. Ropes, Dan H. Ross), 1912-1928 (Box-folder 16 / 10)
    - Ru (correspondents include George C. Rudston, Charles Rule, Rural Spirit, William N. Russ, William G. Russell), 1910-1928 (Box-folder 16 / 11)
    - C.E. Ryan (Great Falls, Mont.), 1914-1918 (Box-folder 16 / 12)
    - Ryrie Brothers (Toronto, Ont.), 1911-1913 (Box-folder 16 / 13)
    - Ry (correspondents include Ethan B. Ryan, Mrs. J.J. Ryan, John D. Ryan, Lawrence B. Ryman), 1912-1928 (Box-folder 16 / 14)
    - P.D. Sanders (Tacoma, Wash.), 1922-1925 (Box-folder 16 / 15)
    - Sam E. Sanders (Desdemona, Tex.), 1924 (Box-folder 16 / 16)
    - Sa (correspondents include C.L. Sackett, St. Peter's Hospital, Salem Nursery Company, Salvation Army, Sands Brothers Dry Goods, Sanford-Evans Company, Max Sarter, Henry J. Sawtell, Sawyer Cattle Company), 1908-1928 (Box-folder 16 / 17)
    - George Schadmann (New York, N.Y.), 1921-1925 (Box-folder 16 / 18)
    - Gustav Schmidt (Killdeer, N.D.), 1920-1924 (Box-folder 16 / 19)
    - Fred Schmitz (Townsend, Mont.), 1920-1928 (Box-folder 16 / 20)
    - Schroeder Brothers Company (Helena, Mont.), 1910-1926 (Box-folder 16 / 21)
    - Adelaide Schulenburg (Chicago, Ill.), 1925-1926 (Box-folder 16 / 22)
    - C.H. Schultz (Bowbells, N.D.), 1927-1928 (Box-folder 16 / 23)
    - Charles L. Scofield (Biddle, Mont.), 1925-1926 (Box-folder 16 / 24)
    - C.B. Scott (Gardiner, Mont.), 1924-1928 (Box-folder 16 / 25)
    - J.E. Scott and Company (Hecla, S.D.), 1922 (Box-folder 16 / 26)
    - Sc (correspondents include Scarsdale Estates, Albert Schlechten, Max Schling, Henry B. Schock, Henry Schubert, A.E. Schwingel, C.E. Scott, Ted Scott), 1909-1928 (Box-folder 16 / 27)
    - L.E. Sedgwick (Christina, Mont.), 1918-1928 (Box-folder 16 / 28)
    - Ralph W. Selkirk (Heart-Bar-L Ranch, Fishtail, Mont.), 1923-1928 (Box-folder 16 / 29)
    - Se (correspondents include J.H. Searle, Ed Sendelbach, Harry Sexton), 1921-1928 (Box-folder 16 / 30)
    - J.A. Shade (Shadeland Herefords, Kingsley, Iowa), 1918-1927 (Box-folder 16 / 31)
    - A.W. Shaw Company (System on the Farm), 1917-1918 (Box-folder 16 / 32)
    - J.H. Shaw (Williston, N.D.), 1918, 1928 (Box-folder 16 / 33)
    - Sheffield Ranch (B.B. Sheffield, Frank Peterson, Calabar, Mont.), 1925-1928 (Box-folder 16 / 34)
    - Court Sheriff; Fred Sheriff (Helena and Canyon Ferry, Mont.), 1917-1919 (Box-folder 16 / 35)
    - J.H. Shober (Shober-Nolan Ranch, Toston, Mont.), 1922-1928 (Box-folder 16 / 36)
    - Sh (correspondents include D.M. Shannon, W.J. Sharp, J.C. Shaubut, B.B. Sheffield, Sam Shepard, W.S. Shore), 1907-1928 (Box-folder 16 / 37)
    - Claude H. Siems (Siems, Helmers and Schaffner, St. Paul, Minn.), 1922-1926 (Box-folder 17 / 1)
    - Silver Bow National Bank (Butte, Mont.), 1908-1922 (Box-folder 17 / 2)
    - John L. Slattery (endorsement for U.S. Attorney for Montana), 1925 (Box-folder 17 / 3)
    - C.C. Slaughter (Dallas, Tex.), 1927-1928 (Box-folder 17 / 4)
    - Si-Sl (correspondents include Harry Siegel, S. Silberman and Sons, J.O. Sinclair, George W. Slack), 1909-1928 (Box-folder 17 / 5)
    - Smith and Morton, Livestock Photographers, 1925-1928 (Box-folder 17 / 6)
    - Charles W. Smith (includes Dept. of Public Health analysis of Cook Stock Farm milk and water), 1918 (Box-folder 17 / 7)
    - R. DeB. Smith (Helena, Mont.), 1911-1918 (Box-folder 17 / 8)
    - Smith (correspondents include Smith Brothers Commission Company, C.A. Smith, H.H. Smith, James S. Smith, M. Smith, Oscar Smith, T.E. Smith, Tom Smith), 1906-1928 (Box-folder 17 / 9)
    - Sn-So (correspondents include George M. Sneider, Snell and Arnott, T.A. Snidow, Sotham Brothers, Southland Cotton Oil Company), 1910-1927 (Box-folder 17 / 10)
    - Spokane Inter State Fair, 1910-1918 (Box-folder 17 / 11)
    - Sp (correspondents include C.A. Spaulding, R.J. Spear, Sperry Realty and Investment Company, Spokane and Eastern Trust Company, Spreckles Sugar Company, Josephine Spriggs, J.L. Sprinkle), 1910-1928 (Box-folder 17 / 12)
    - Emil Starz, Pharmacist (includes report on Cook Stock Farm water), 1916-1923 (Box-folder 17 / 13)
    - State Nursery and Seed Company (Helena, Mont.), 1918-1928 (Box-folder 17 / 14)
    - F.B. Stearns Company (Cleveland, Ohio), 1920-1923 (Box-folder 17 / 15)
    - H.S. Stephenson (El Paso, Tex.), 1925-1928 (Box-folder 17 / 16)
    - Sam Stephenson (Great Falls, Mont.), 1917-1924 (Box-folder 17 / 17)
    - E.W. Stetson (Butte and Warm Springs, Mont.), 1907-1925 (Box-folder 17 / 18)
    - F.R. Stevens (New York, N.Y.), 1915-1918 (Box-folder 17 / 19)
    - I. Thayer Stevens (Harlowton, Mont.), 1927-1928 (Box-folder 17 / 20)
    - H.L. Stewart (New York, N.Y.), 1915-1918 (Box-folder 17 / 21)
    - P.S. Streit (Moore, Mont.), 1928 (Box-folder 17 / 22)
    - Allis Brown Stuart (Mrs. Granville Stuart), 1925 (Box-folder 17 / 23)
    - J.G. Stuart (Hill Cattle Corporation, Livingston, Mont.), 1922-1928 (Box-folder 17 / 24)
    - St (correspondents include Standard Garage, James T. Stanford, Herman Steen, William Stewart, Stockgrowers Inc., F. Thayer Stoddard, J.B. Stoker, Claude E. Storm, B.F. Stranahan, V.B. Strong, John Sturrock Plumbing and Heating Company), 1907-1928 (Box-folder 17 / 25)
    - Suffolk Storage Warehouse Company (re shipment of Mrs. Cook's goods), 1909 (Box-folder 17 / 26)
    - Su-Sw (correspondents include George Sucin re Rumanian sheepherders, D.E. Sullivan, Harry L. Summers, Sunburst Oil and Gas Company, Sunburst Refining Company, W.I. Sutcliff, Neil Sutherland, Stanley Swaim, A.D. Swan, Sweet Brothers, Charles R. Swift), 1907-1928 (Box-folder 17 / 27)
    - William S. Tash (DL Ranch, Bannack, Mont.), 1922-1928 (Box-folder 17 / 28)
    - Ta (correspondents include William Howard Taft, T.P. Talle, Tanawax Pheasantry, J. Taylor), 1911-1928 (Box-folder 17 / 29)
    - Terrell's Aquatic Farm (Clyde B. Terrell, plants for wildlife habitat), 1919-1927 (Box-folder 17 / 30)
    - Te (correspondents include C.D. and Julian Terrett, Teton County offices, Texas Hereford Association), 1908-1927 (Box-folder 17 / 31)
    - L.W. Thompson (Mondak, Mont.), 1925-1926 (Box-folder 17 / 32)
    - Notley Thompson (aide to Thomas A. Marlow), 1913-1918 (Box-folder 17 / 33)
    - Herman and Melvin Thor (Oramia, Minn.), 1922-1928 (Box-folder 17 / 34)
    - D. Thronson (Chicago and Marseilles, Ill.), 1910-1911 (Box-folder 17 / 35)
    - Th-Ti (correspondents include R.C. Thatcher, Henry Thiessen, I.W. Thomas, William Thomlinson, Lester H. Thompson, Thoroughbred Horse Association, Russell Thorp, I.H. Thurman, R.E. Thurston, G.D. Tilley naturalist), 1914-1928 (Box-folder 17 / 36)
    - Harriet W. Tooley (Harlowton, Mont.), 1922-1924 (Box-folder 18 / 1)
    - Cyrus A. Tow (Norway, Iowa), 1918-1928 (Box-folder 18 / 2)
    - To (correspondents include W.H. Tobey, Arthur Todhunter, Nathaniel Tonkin, William Tonn, John R. Toole, E.A. Tostevin), 1907-1928 (Box-folder 18 / 3)
    - A.O. Trumbull (Miles City, Mont.), 1923 (Box-folder 18 / 4)
    - Tr-Tw (correspondents include Tractor and Equipment Company, Benjamin Turner, J.E. Turner, T.J. Twedt, Twin City Land Company, Twin Falls North Side Land and Water Company), 1907-1928 (Box-folder 18 / 5)
    - United States. Bureau of Animal Industry (includes U.S. Sheep Experiment Stations in Miles City, Mont., and Dubois, Idaho), 1915-1928 (Box-folder 18 / 6)
    - United States. Forest Service, District 1; Wasatch National Forest, 1919-1920 (Box-folder 18 / 7)
    - United States. Forest Service, Helena National Forest (correspondents include J.B. Seely, C.K. McHarg, Arthur H. Abbott), 1916-1927 (Box-folder 18 / 8)
    - United States. Forest Service, Jefferson National Forest (correspondents include Scott Leavitt, W.B. Willey), 1916-1924 (Box-folder 18 / 9)
    - United States. Office of Indian Affairs, 1917-1921 (Box-folder 18 / 10)
    - United States. Indian Field Service (Colville Agency, Crow Agency, Fort Apache, Fort Belknap), 1917-1928 (Box-folder 18 / 11)
    - United States. Indian Field Service (Fort Berthoud, Fort Hall), 1922-1926 (Box-folder 18 / 12)
    - United States. Indian Field Service (Pine Ridge, Rocky Boy), 1923-1927 (Box-folder 18 / 13)
    - United States. Indian Field Service (Tongue River Agency), 1926-1928 (Box-folder 18 / 14)
    - United States. Internal Revenue Service, 1924, 1927 (Box-folder 18 / 15)
    - United States. [miscellaneous agencies], 1915-1924 (Box-folder 18 / 16)
    - United States Fidelity and Guaranty Company, 1915 (Box-folder 18 / 17)
    - United States Live Stock Sanitary Association, 1922-1923 (Box-folder 18 / 18)
    - University of Idaho Experiment Station, 1915-1919 (Box-folder 18 / 19)
    - University of Wyoming Agricultural College and Experiment Station, 1916-1923 (Box-folder 18 / 20)
    - Paul E. Utz (White Sulphur Springs, Mont.), 1918-1919 (Box-folder 18 / 21)
    - U (correspondents include Union Bank and Trust Company, Union Stockyards Company of Ohaha, United Stockmen's Association for Federal Control of Public Grazing Lands, Utah State Fair Association), 1906-1928 (Box-folder 18 / 22)
    - Peter Van Hoven (St. Paul, Minn.), 1921 (Box-folder 18 / 23)
    - Ralph Van Vechten (Chicago, Ill., includes estate), 1923-1928 (Box-folder 18 / 24)
    - George C. Vogt (Sula, Mont.), 1925-1928 (Box-folder 18 / 25)
    - V (correspondents include Valier Farm Sales Company, H.P. Van Epps, George B. Vaughan, A. Vaux, S.H. Velie, B.F. Voodman, Joseph Vook), 1909-1913 (Box-folder 18 / 26)
    - Charles Wake (England), 1909-1913 (Box-folder 18 / 27)
    - Mrs. William Wallace (Wallace Ranch, Missoula, Mont.), 1925-1928 (Box-folder 18 / 28)